freelottocasino.com 2013-05-05

# FreeLottoCasino :: Privacy Policy

|  This privacy statement covers the site [www.freelottocasino.com](http://www.freelottocasino.com/) (FLC). Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FLC does not own or control, or to people that FLC does not employ or manage. 

**_Surveys and Contests_**  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site (contest terms). If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as email, name, and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use collected information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic and/or personalize the site, and to send participants an email newsletter. 

We use may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

**_Cookies_**  
FLC may set and access FLC cookies on your computer. FLC allows other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to FLC cookies. 

**_Log Files_**  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

**_Choice_**  
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. 

**_Links to Other Sites_**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by FLC. Please be aware that we, FLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**_Security_**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**_Changes in this Privacy Statement_**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
